http://www.nutmegstatefcu.org/privacy-policy/

Home*COVID-19*NewsATM LocationsBranch Hours & LocationsAbout UsCareersContact UsEspañol
Home
English/ESPAñOL
Home*COVID-19*NewsRecent Fraud Against State Unemployment Insurance ProgramsATM LocationsBranch Hours & LocationsMilford - DMV Express & Nutmeg State FCUNorth Haven - DMV Express & Nutmeg State FCUAbout UsBecome a MemberBecome a VolunteerCareersFrequently Asked Questions (FAQ)Holiday ClosingsMeet the Senior ManagementMeet the Supervisory CommitteeMeet the Branch ManagementMission StatementMeet the BoardPresident's BlogCareersContact UsLoansApply for a LoanAuto LoansEducation LoansHome Equity LoansHomeowners ExpressMoneyline Line of CreditMortgage LoansOnline Loan PaymentsPersonal LoansSkip-A-PaymentSmart-E LoansMastercard® Credit CardWorking Wheels Car Ownership ProgramAccountsAdditional ServicesCertificatesChecking & ATM/Debit CardClub AccountsHealth Savings AccountsIRAsKidz Club AccountsMoney Market AccountsRegular Share SavingsStatus CheckingSave For A Purpose - Juntos AhorramosBusinessBusiness BankingBusiness CheckingBusiness LoansBusiness SavingsElectronic ServicesMerchant ServicesApply for a Business LoanBusiness Credit CardRatesBusiness RatesLoan RatesSavings RatesCalculatorsLoan CalculatorMortgage Loan CalculatorSavings CalculatorServicese-Bankinge-CheckImagese-Depositse-HomeEquitye-Mortgagee-Loanse-Paye-StatementsMobile BankingCard Manager AppText and e-Mail AlertsMobile PayCredit Report ResourcesID Theft ServicePayroll Deduction and Direct DepositPrivilege PayVoicelineInvestmentsThe Family Security Plan®DMV ExpressSchedule a DMV Express AppointmentFresh Start ServicesBranch AppointmentsInsuranceHome InsuranceRenters InsuranceAuto InsuranceMotorcycle InsuranceLife InsuranceBusiness InsuranceEspañolAcerca de NosotrosHágase SocioHágase VoluntarioOportunidades de EmpleoPreguntas ComunesNuestra MisiónProductos de PréstamoPréstamo de AutoLínea de crédito MoneylinePréstamos PersonalesPréstamos para educaciónPrestamos de Garantía HipotecariaHipoteca Pápida Para Los PropietariosPréstamos hipotecariosPagos de prestamos en lineaPrograma de propiedad de vehículos “Working Wheels”Productos de AhorroCertificadosClub AccountsIRAsCuentas Kidz ClubMoney MarketCuenta de Ahorros SencilloComprobación del estadoServicios AdicionalesCuentas de Cheques y ATM/DebitJuntos AhorramosNegocioCuenta de Cheques para NegociosPrestamos para NegociosCuenta de Ahorro para NegociosServicios ElectronicosServiciose-BancoImágenes de cheques electrónicosPago electrónicoRécords electrónicosRobo de IdentidadBancario móvilDeducción de Nómina y Depósito DirectoAlertas electrónicasVoicelineContáctenosCoronavirus Readiness: Bank 24/7 From AnywhereHoras extendidas de sucursales y centros de contacto
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
The purpose of the Privacy Statement is to detail Nutmeg State Financial Credit Union’s practices for safeguarding personal financial information, and to inform account holders that they have the ability to “opt-out” of the information sharing process in certain cases. For the full content of our Privacy Statement please click here.
Deposit Account
Loan Account
Credit Card
We will tell you the sources for nonpublic personal information we collect on our members. We will also inform you to what measures we take to secure that information.
We will also tell you what information we share with other entities. We will explain what your rights are, and how you can exercise them. If you share your account relationship with someone else, for example where you are a co-borrower or joint holder of a share draft account, we suggest that you share this information with each other to ensure that each of you are aware of our policy and your options.
We first define some terms.
Non public personal information means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources such as telephone directories or government records. An affiliate is a company we own or control. A nonaffiliated third party is a company that is not an affiliate of ours. Opt out means a choice you can make to prevent certain sharing of information. We will explain how you can exercise this choice.
The Information That We Collect
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on your applications or other forms
Information about your transactions with us
Information about your transactions with nonaffiliated third parties
Information from a consumer reporting agency
The Confidentiality, Security and Integrity of Your Nonpublic Personal Information
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. Nonpublic personal information accessible or transmitted over the Internet is protected using a secure SSL connection.
Nonpublic Personal Information and Nonaffiliated Third Parties
Non public information we receive from you on an application or other form, such as:
Name
Address
Social security number
You may opt out of the disclosure of the information listed above.
Exceptions:
We do not share this information about members who reside in Vermont.
We do not share any information derived from deposit (share) relationships with us about members who reside in Mississippi.
The only information we share about our members from Tennessee is name and address.
Types of Nonaffiliated Third Parties
We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to the following types of nonaffiliated third parties:
Financial service providers, such as
Insurance agents
Future Nonaffiliated Third Party Disclosure
We also reserve the right to disclose the following additional nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties in the future:
Nonpublic personal information about your transactions with us, such as
Types of accounts
Nonpublic personal information about your transactions with nonaffiliated third parties, such as
Credit card usage
You may opt out of this disclosure of the information listed above.
We may disclose this nonpublic personal information with the nonaffiliated third parties listed under the heading Types of Nonaffiliated Third Parties, as well as the following additional nonaffiliated third parties:
Financial service providers, such as
Mortgage bankers
Nonpublic Information and Other Parties
We do not disclose your nonpublic personal information to anyone, except as permitted by law or as disclosed in this disclosure.
Nonpublic Personal Information and Former Members
We do not disclose nonpublic personal information about former members, except as permitted by law.
Your Right to Block the Disclosure of Your Nonpublic Personal Information
Nonaffiliated Third Parties. If you do not want us to share your nonpublic personal information with nonaffiliated third parties, you can block the release of certain nonpublic personal information. This is known as your right to “opt out.”Your decision to block the disclosure of your nonpublic personal information will apply to all products and services you receive from us.
If you have a joint account, each participant of this account has a separate right to opt out. If one of you chooses to opt out of the disclosure of nonpublic personal information, and the other does not, only information regarding the party who does not opt out will be disclosed. Any participant on the account can opt out of the behalf of any other participant of the account.
If you wish to opt out of disclosures, you may do so by using the following methods:
Contact the credit union at: Nutmeg State Financial Credit Union, 520 Cromwell Avenue, PO Box 66, Rocky Hill, CT 06067-0066.
Click here to send us an e-mail expressing that you would not like us to share your nonpublic personal information with nonaffiliated third parties.
For a complete copy of this disclosure, call 860-513-5000 (local) or 1-800-526-6933 (nationwide).
Back to Top
ABOUT NUTMEG STATE FINANCIAL CREDIT UNION
Nutmeg State Financial Credit Union (NSFCU) is a member-owned, not-for-profit financial cooperative headquartered in Rocky Hill, Connecticut. We practice the philosophy of returning profits to our members in the form of excellent rates, programs, services and more. Since its founding in 1936, NSFCU has become one of the most prominent and innovative credit unions in the United States. As we continue to grow, we will stand by our mission to revolutionize the banking industry with technology while also providing an exceptional member experience.
Your savings are federally insured to at least $250,000 and backed by the full faith and credit of the United States Government.
National Credit Union Administration (NCUA), a U.S. Government Agency
